[{"answer": "Say, that place", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "It is not far at all, and it is a beautiful place. And your big brother is abbott there. You will not be alone", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "It is not far at all, and it is a beautiful place. And your big brother is abbott there. You will not be alone", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You will be fine. You will be a fine monk", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You have all the room", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You move", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You could buy them", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What do you think", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Do I have money", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Do you have money", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "You can't do anything real until you are my friend", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Not until you are eighteen", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "True suffering arises from contaminated actions and afflictions.  Birth, illness, grief, old age, poverty, pain, death", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "The causes of suffering arise from true sources.  Attachment, desire, envy, hatred, greed, unkindness, wrong view and so forth", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Will we be in this war", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Will we ever be in war", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "my friend, I understand there was an attempt on your life", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You are unharmed", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yes.  As a free country. But our attempts have proven futile.  We continue to be badly outmaneuvered by the Chinese", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "that place is a newly independent nation.  They are struggling. that place is in no position to help us", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Can that place help us", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "that place is a newly independent nation.  They are struggling. that place is in no position to help us", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "that place chooses not to", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "that place", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "And, that place", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "that place chooses not to", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "that place, we shall see", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I will miss you", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "We have", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "We have had fun, you and I. Fun for a little boy in an old palace", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You have grown up very good", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "We have", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "And you have grown older and your chin has grown balder", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Much too young", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "This little brother was terribly sweet.  When he died, my mother was so sad.  A lama said to her, before the little brother was laid out for burial, take a bit of butter and rub a spot on his skin.  He will come back to you, you will see. So, my mother did this, and a few years later, a new boy was born", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "He does, a little spot where the butter had been", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Have you heard the terms of the Seventeen Point Agreement", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I have a copy for you", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I accept your resignations", "docId": "kundun.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "There will be no new Prime Ministers", "qsentId": 42}]